http://www.unitherm.co.at/en/contact/terms

HomeProductsServiceAbout usContactNewsDownloads
Navigation
ProductsM.A.S Kiln BurnerM.A.S.DTCalciner BurnersBurner AccessoriesHot Gas GeneratorsFuel Supply SystemsSecondary FuelsServiceAfter SalesSpare PartsAbout usAbout usReference listCareerUNITHERM GroupContactContact UsTerms/Legal noticeNewsNewsletter sign upLatest NewsDownloads
Contact UsTerms/Legal notice
HomeContactTerms/Legal notice
Privacy Policy
Please read this Privacy Policy and the Disclaimer before using this web site. By using this web site you agree to the Privacy Policy and accept the Disclaimer.Unitherm Cemcon has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.This web site contains links to other sites. Unitherm Cemcon is not responsible for the privacy practices or the contents of such other web sites.
TrackingUnitherm Cemcon automatically tracks how the content provided is used. This tracking allows us to gain a better understanding of potential areas for improvement so as to continually improve the relevance of and accessibility to the content we provide. Such usage information will not be in a form which may be traced to identifiable individual persons.This usage information will only be used within Unitherm Cemcon to increase the quality of content, service and support to our visitors.
Legal notice and disclaimerThis web site is meant as an introduction to the activities of Unitherm Cemcon. Please read this Legal Notice and Disclaimer and the Privacy Policy before using this web site. By using this web site you accept the terms and conditions set out in this Legal Notice and Disclaimer and consent to the Privacy Policy.
CopyrightYou may download material displayed on this web site only for non-commercial and personal use and provided you respect and keep intact all copyright, trademark and other proprietary notices. You may not copy, reproduce, republish, up-load, post, transmit or distribute in any way the contents of this web site including the text, images, audio and video for either public or commercial use or communication, without prior written permission from Unitherm Cemcon.
TrademarksThe trademarks and logos displayed on this web site, are trademarks of Unitherm Cemcon. Nothing contained on the site may be construed as granting, by implication or otherwise, any licence or right to use any of the trademarks displayed on this site without the prior written permission of Unitherm Cemcon.
DisclaimerThis web site has been made in accordance with Austrian law. Reasonable care is being taken to ensure that the site content is accurate and up-to-date, however, Unitherm Cemcon makes no warranties or representations about accuracy, sequence, timeliness or completeness of this web site's content and may discontinue distributing the site without prior notice. The information on this site is intended for general guidance only.
Unitherm Cemcon disclaims any control over, relationship with, or endorsement of sites to which this site is linked.Unitherm Cemcon shall not be liable for any loss whether direct, indirect, incidental or consequential, arising out of access to, use of or reliance upon any of the content on this web site or sites to which this web site is linked regardless of whether such content has been accurate or complete and Unitherm Cemcon will not pay any damages whether for loss or injury, punitive or otherwise because of any such access to, use of or reliance upon any of the content on this web site or sites to which this web site is linked.
Contacting Unitherm CemconIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this web site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact: sales@unitherm.at
Cookies
To make this site work properly, we sometimes place small data files called cookies on your device. Most big websites do this too.
What are cookies? A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another.
How do we use cookies? Cookies do not contain any information that personally identifies you, but personal information that we store about you may be linked, by us, to the information stored in and obtained from cookies. The cookies used on the website include those which are strictly necessary cookies for access and navigation, cookies that track usage (performance cookies), remember your choices (functionality cookies), and cookies that provide you with targeted content or advertising. We may use the information we obtain from your use of our cookies for the following purposes:
to recognise your computer when you visit the website
to improve the website's usability
to analyse the use of the website
in the administration of the website
How to control cookies You can control and/or delete cookies as you wish – for details, see aboutcookies.org. You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work.
Unitherm Cemcon
Feuerungsanlagen GmbH
Pfarrgasse 601230 ViennaAustria
Phone: +43 1 74041-0Fax: +43 1 74041-28E-Mail: sales@unitherm.at
Commercial registry number: 398377 zCommercial register court: HG WienVAT Reg. No.: ATU 68170034
Chamber membership: Austrian Federal Economic Chamber Legal form: limited company
Scroll to top
ProductsM.A.S Kiln BurnerCalciner BurnersBurner AccessoriesHot Gas GeneratorsFuel Supply SystemsSecondary FuelsServiceAfter SalesSpare PartsAbout usAbout usReference listCareerUNITHERM GroupContactContact UsTerms/Legal noticeNewsNewsletter sign upLatest NewsDownloads
Scroll to top
Unitherm Cemcon Feuerungsanlagen GmbH · 1230 Vienna · Pfarrgasse 60 · Austria · Europe Phone +43 1 74041-0 · Fax +43 1 74041-28 · sales@unitherm.at Follow us on
Unitherm Cemcon Feuerungsanlagen GmbH
1230 Vienna · Pfarrgasse 60 · Austria · Europe
Phone +43 1 74041-0
Fax +43 1 74041-28 · sales@unitherm.at
Follow us on
